Guide to the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District Lodge 751 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District Lodge 751 records
1937-2017
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
6182
6182-001
International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers.$bDistrict Lodge 751
21.5 cubic feet 25 boxes and 1 OS folder
Materials relating to the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District Lodge 751 and their activities
The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District Lodge No. 751 traces its origins to the founding of Local Lodge 751 of the International Association of Machinists at the Boeing Airplane Company in 1935. This local union organized Boeing on an industrial rather than craft basis. The first collective bargaining agreement with Boeing was signed July 1, 1936. A union shop was established with the second contract, in 1937. The union was re-organized as District Lodge No. 751 in 1941. It now consists of local lodges 751-A (assembly and production workers), 751-C (machinists), 751-E (electronics workers), 751-F (inspectors, clerks, others), Local 86 (workers in Spokane area), Local 1123 (workers in Wenatchee area and Grand Coulee Dam), and Local 1951 (Richland).
Union governance records include District Lodge 751 council minutes, membership records, and records of union officer elections. Collective bargaining records include negotiation records and contacts with the Boeing Company (1943-1999) as well as records relating to strikes such as video recordings. Records of the District Lodge's Labor History Committee include publications on union history, video interviews with union activists, and memorabilia. Press and publicity records include clipping documenting press coverage of the union and its activities as well as items relating to the IAMAW's activities in the community. Records include numerous artifacts, including badges and pins, stickers and patches, and apparel related to the union and allied organizations.
Forms a part of the Labor Archives of Washington
Collection contains some film formats.
No restrictions on access.
Donated by District Lodge 751. Point person Tom Lux with approval of Sue Palmer IAM District 751 Secretary-Treasurer. 2017-01-19
One film of the Bel Canto Championship Choir, Franklin High School, Christmas program was transferred to the Seattle Public School District Archives.
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor Unions; Labor History
- INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF MACHINISTS AND AEROSPACE WORKERS DISTRICT LODGE No. 751, 1937-2017; RECORD GROUP 1
  - MINUTES, 1943-1979; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/1 - 2/6)
    - District Council minutes, 1943 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - District Council minutes, 1944 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - District Council minutes - copy 1 (part 1 of 2), 1945 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - District Council minutes - copy 1 (part 2 of 2), 1945 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - District Council minutes - copy 2 (part 1 of 2), 1945 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - District Council minutes - copy 2 (part 2 of 2), 1945 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - District Council minutes - copy 1 (part 1 of 2), 1946 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - District Council minutes - copy 1 (part 2 of 2), 1946 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - District Council minutes - copy 2 (part 1 of 2), 1946 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - District Council minutes - copy 2 (part 2 of 2), 1946 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - District Council minutes - copy 1 (part 1 of 2), 1947 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - District Council minutes - copy 1 (part 2 of 2), 1947 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - District Council minutes - copy 2 (part 1 of 2), 1947 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - District Council minutes - copy 2 (part 2 of 2), 1947 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - District Council minutes (part 1 of 3), 1948 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - District Council minutes (part 2 of 3), 1948 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - District Council minutes (part 3 of 3), 1948 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - District Council minutes (part 1 of 2), 1949 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - District Council minutes (part 2 of 2), 1949 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - District Council minutes (part 1 of 2), 1950 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - District Council minutes (part 2 of 2), 1950 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - District Council minutes, 1977 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - District Council minutes, 1978 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Local Lodge 751-C minutes, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Aeronautical Machinists, Inc. Board of Trustees minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - OFFICER AND MEMBERSHIP RECORDS, SERIES 2
    - MEMBERSHIP RECORDS, 1945-1966; SUBSERIES 1 (Box-folder 2/7 - 3/16)
      - Delegate and committee membership lists, 1945-1950 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Local Lodge 751C record of transfers, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Lists of applicants for membership, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Certified letter list, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - A, 1965 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - B (1 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - B (2 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - C, 1965 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - D, 1965 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - E, 1965 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - F, 1965 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - G, 1965 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - H, 1965 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - I/J, 1965 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - K, 1965 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - L, 1965 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - M (1 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - M (2 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - N, 1965 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - O, 1965 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - P/Q, 1965 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - R, 1965 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - S (1 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - S (2 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - T, 1965 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - U/V, 1965 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - W (1 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - W (2 of 2), 1965 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Original certified letters opting out of union membership - X/Y/Z, 1965 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - OFFICER ELECTION RECORDS, 1967-2007; SUBSERIES 2 (Box-folder 4/1 - 4/6)
      - 1977 District Election Charges (Box-folder 4/1)
      - District 751 officers: posters, 1986; undated (Box-folder 4/2)
      - District 751 election materials, 2007 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - District 751 President campaign flyers, 2007 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - William M. Hanson election campaign card, 1967 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Union election flyers and letter, 1986 (Box-folder 4/6)
  - COLLECTIVE BARGAINING AND AGREEMENT RECORDS, SERIES 3
    - NEGOTIATION RECORDS, 1943-1999; SUBSERIES 1 (Box-folder 4/7 - 5/22)
      - Boeing collective bargaining agreement, 1943 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (part 1 of 2), 1958 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (part 2 of 2), 1958 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Proposed Industry-Wide Contract International Association of Machinists Boeing Airplane Company, 1958 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Boeing Airplane Company Employee Retirement Plan Report of 1958 Operations (Box-folder 4/11)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (1 of 2), 1959 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (2 of 2), 1959 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Collective Bargaining Agreement Between Boeing Airplane Company and International Assn. of Machinists, AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Contract proposal ballot, 1960 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (1 of 2), 1960 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (2 of 2), 1960 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (1 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 4/18)
      - Boeing Airplane Company negotiations (2 of 2), 1961 (Box-folder 4/19)
      - The Boeing Company General Correspondence, 1961 (Box-folder 4/20)
      - The Boeing Company - arbitrator correspondence, 1961 (Box-folder 4/21)
      - The Boeing Company (negotiations) (1 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 4/22)
      - The Boeing Company (negotiations) (2 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - The Boeing Company (negotiations) (1 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 4/24)
      - The Boeing Company (negotiations) (2 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 4/25)
      - The Boeing Company (negotiations) (3 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 4/26)
      - The Boeing Company - correspondence re negotiations, meetings, strikes, etc. (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - The Boeing Company - correspondence re negotiations, meetings, strikes, etc. (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Union contract proposal -- May, 1965 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Union contract proposal -- July 15, 1965 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - The Boeing Company - negotiations, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - The Boeing Company - travel pay Inequity, 1966 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Boeing Coordinating Council correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Union contract proposal to Boeing Company, 1968 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Manpower Control Committee, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Boeing Company collective bargaining agreement pamphlets, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Town of Milton collective bargaining agreement, 1987 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Proposed contract changes, 1986 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Federal Mediator's proposed contract settlement between IAM&AW and Boeing, 1989 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Contract update training instructor's guide, 1990 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Contract update, 1990 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Contract update, 1992 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - 1995 Contract survey (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Contract surveys, 1999 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Contract update, 1999 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Union Power '99, 1999 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Contract proposals, 1999 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Requests for time off for union business, 1978 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - STRIKE RECORDS, 1965-1999; SUBSERIES 2 (Box-folder 5/23 - 6/19, 7)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - A, 1965 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - B, 1965 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - C, 1965 (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - D, 1965 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - E, 1965 (Box-folder 5/27)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - F, 1965 (Box-folder 5/28)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - G, 1965 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - H, 1965 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - J, 1965 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - K, 1965 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - L, 1965 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - M, 1965 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - N, 1965 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - O, 1965 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - P, 1965 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - R, 1965 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - S, 1965 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - T, 1965 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - U/V, 1965 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - W, 1965 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Strikebreaking Certified Letters - Z and Unsorted, 1965 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Receipts for payments from strike fund, 1965 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - 1999 Strike scrapbook - photocopy (Box-folder 6/16)
      - 1999 Strike scrapbook contents - pages 1-20 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - 1999 Strike scrapbook contents - pages 21-52 (Box-folder 6/18)
      - 1999 Strike scrapbook contents - pages 53-76 (Box-folder 6/19)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1968-2009; SERIES 4 (Box-folder 6/20 - 6/27)
    - International Association of Machinists 751 Auditor Reports, Financial Statements, Budgets, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - Financial Officers' Reference Manual (part 1 of 3), 2009 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Financial Officers' Reference Manual (part 2 of 3), 2009 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - Financial Officers' Reference Manual (part 3 of 3), 2009 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - ADP payroll system, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - VLM membership program analysis, 2006 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Financial officers' seminar, 2006 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Union dues notebook, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 6/27)
  - SUBJECT FILES, 1955-2016; SERIES 5 (Box-folder 6/28 - 6/39, 8/1 - 9/1)
    - The Boeing Company - United Welders of America, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - "Charges" - How to File Info from International re Strikes, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 6/29)
    - Death Benefit Procedures, 1974 (Box-folder 6/30)
    - Supersonic Transport, 1971 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Reciprocal transfer agreements with IAM, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Expense Report Procedure and Meeting Outline, 1968 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Complete contract for Aero Union Building for Aeronautical Industrial Dist. Lodge 751, 1955 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Bill from District 130 for 2 watches, 1980 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Machinists Non Partisan League - minutes, bylaws, contributions (1 of 4), 1973-1978 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Machinists Non Partisan League - minutes, bylaws, contributions (2 of 4), 1973-1978 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Machinists Non Partisan League - minutes, bylaws, contributions (3 of 4), 1973-1978 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Machinists Non Partisan League - minutes, bylaws, contributions (4 of 4), 1973-1978 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - International Association of Machinists Aerospace Industry Conference - 751 Report, 1969 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - International Association of Machinists Aerospace Report, 1969 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - International Association of Machinists Northwest Territory Staff Conference, 1969 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - July honor roll, 1980 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Overtime policies, 1982 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Concession bargaining, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Teamsters/International Association of Machinists correspondence over raiding, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Coalition of Labor and Business (COLAB) Bylaws and Minutes, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - COLAB Minutes, Articles of Incorporation, Member Lists, Dues, and Balance Sheets, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - AIR Washington - Expanding Sea-Tac Capacity and Press Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - COLAB Minutes, Bylaws and Balance Sheets, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - COLAB Membership, Minutes, Press Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - Regional Transit Project Plans, 1991 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - COLAB Executive Director Resumes, 1991 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Metro 2000 Project, 1991 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - COLAB Mission Statement, Articles, Early Documents, 1991 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Skilled trades report, 1969 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Sue Palmer awards and certificates, 1993-2005 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Boeing Christmas party program, 1979 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - Election recommendations, 1988 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - Schrontz's Nightmare - strike publication, 1995 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - Union concerns - self inspection and acceptance, 2000 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Process specification departure, 1975 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Boeing Company. Retirement Plan, 1993 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Military pay differential, 1993 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - Everett safety glasses policy, 1998 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Mediation agreement over sick leave, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - Two week 747 line shutdown, 1992 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - Strut modification program, 1994 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Manpower Committee shift preference, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - Management attributes assessment process, 1994 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Work shifts and schedules for full time employees, 1994 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Occupational health qualification program, 1994 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Boeing policy on transexualism, 1993 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Consolidation of facilities, 1994 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Drug and alcohol testing changes, 1994 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Benefits worth fighting for! - leaflet, c. 2016 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Parliamentary procedure, 2001 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Keys to a successful strike, 1996 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Health care survey results Boeing: Puget Sound, Wichita, Portland, 2001 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Understanding Sexual Harassment, 2001 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - International Association of Machinists HPWO Partnerships Field Manual, Undated (Box-folder 8/1)
    - International Association of Machinists General Organizing Drive Materials, 1991 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - International Association of Machinists In-Plant Organizing Team Manual, Undated (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Laid-off Worker Services Guide, c. 1999 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Boeing health insurance, 1985 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women photos, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Washington State Labor Council Women's Committee, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Women's Summer School, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Jackie Boschok materials, 2007-2010 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), c. 1980-2000 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - International Association of Machinists events, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - LABOR HISTORY COMMITTEE RECORDS, 1948-2016; SERIES 6 (Box-folder 9/2 - 9/9, 11/1 - 13/15)
    - Labor History Committee Materials, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - The Boeing Dispute: a Study in Pictures, 1948 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - International Association of Machinists AW 125 Years of Making History, 2013 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - District 751 Historical Reference Book, 2012 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - IAM 751 Union History, c. 2008 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Excerpt from The Family, by Jeff Sharlet, c. 2009 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - 747 Dreamliner first flight, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Boeing Plant 2 - 75+ years, 2010 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Oral History - Jerry Dargitz, 2010 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Oral History - Ron McGaha interviewed by Tom Lux and Dave Swan, 2010 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Oral History - Ruth Render interviewed by Tom Lux, 2013 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Oral History - Mary King, 2012 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Oral History - James Hershey, 2010 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Oral History - Jerry Dargitz (2), 2011 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Oral History - Ken Lonn Interview and Sculptures, 2014 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Oral History - Harold Wilson, 2015 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Oral History - John McGinnis, 2015 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Oral History - Al Wydick, 2011 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Oral History - Linda Sims, 2014 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Oral History - Don Clement, 2014 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Oral History - Carl Schwartz, 2012 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Boeing-Union parts 1 & 2, 1985 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Boeing-Union parts 3 & 4, 1985 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - 11-12-95 Strike tape, 1995 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Everett rally -- Sweeney, Trumka, Chavez-Thompson, 1995 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - News 7, News 5 -- strike sanction 9-19-83 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - IAM&AW District Lodge 751 8-19-80 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - IAM Machinists contract with the community, undated (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Jo Marie / Roman tribute, undated (Box-folder 12/3)
    - John McCann - Blood in the Water - KIRO, 12-27-1989 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Strike tape, 1995 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Strike tape - march in Seattle 10-11-95, 1995 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Ride for My Job - striking bikers and supporters 11-2-95, 1995 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Strike tape #1, 1995 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Strike 11-10-95 to 11-24-95 at headquarters and in Snohomish, 1995 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Boeing-Union parts 1 & 2, 1985 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Boeing-Union parts 3 & 4, 1985 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - 1995 strike video #1 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - 1995 strike video #2 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - 1995 strike video #3 -- march in Seattle 10-11-95 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - 1995 strike video #4 -- Ride for my job; footage and news coverage (Box-folder 12/15)
    - 1995 strike video #5 -- Headquarters and in Snohomish (Box-folder 12/16)
    - 1995 strike video #6 -- Everett rally 11-12-95 (part 1 of 2) (Box-folder 12/17)
    - 1995 strike video #7 -- Everett rally 11-12-95 (part 2 of 2) (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Rise Up! Productions. Boeing Jet Airliner, 1995 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Derek Morgan and friends. Celebrating the IAM: a proud century of union songs, 1988 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Rise Up! Productions. Boeing Jet Airliner, 1995 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Derek Morgan and friends. Celebrating the IAM: a proud century of union songs, 1988 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Maritime speaker at Washington State Labor Council, undated (Box-folder 13/11)
    - Boeing arbitration hearing (part 1 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Boeing arbitration hearing (part 2 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Boeing arbitration hearing (part 3 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - 50 year org, 1985? (Box-folder 13/15)
  - PRESS AND PUBLICITY RECORDS, 1937-2009; SERIES 7 (Box-folder 9/10 - 10/13, OS, 12/19 - 13/6)
    - Puyallup Daffodil Parade press coverage, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Proposed contract changes, 1977 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - 751 Aero Mechanic issues, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Coverage of 1989 Boeing strike (Box-folder 9/13)
    - The Machinist and AFL-CIO news coverage of 1989 Boeing strike (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer coverage of 1989 Boeing strike (1 of 2) (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Seattle Times and Seattle Post-Intelligencer coverage of 1989 Boeing strike (2 of 2) (Box-folder 9/16)
    - 1989 Strike press clippings (1 of 3) (Box-folder 9/17)
    - 1989 Strike press clippings (2 of 3) (Box-folder 9/18)
    - 1989 Strike press clippings (3 of 3) (Box-folder 9/19)
    - 1989 Contract proposals and press (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Complete set of flyers pre-contract, 1989 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Walking the Line in '89 Boeing on Strike, 1989 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Pre-contract proposals and flyers, 1992 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - 1995 Strike press coverage (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Contract '95 flyers, 1995 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - NLRB charges, 1995 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Contract proposal highlights, 1995 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Contract flyers, 1999 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - Aero Mechanic and news coverage, 1999 (Box-folder 9/29)
    - Contract proposal and press coverage, 2002 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - Longacres feature race photographs, 1990 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Aeromechanics Day Purse, 1990 (Box-folder 9/1)